哦  谢谢帮忙挑水  丽芙
Oh, thanks for fetching the water, liv.
你错过了一个美好的早晨
You missed a wonderful wake.
好了  现在玛蒂那组已经出局了
Yeah, and now with Maddie out of the game,
我们也许真的有击败妈妈的好机会
We might actually have a chance at beating mom.
她没必要把所有的柴禾都
She did have to trade in all her firewood
换成葬花啊
For funeral flowers.
噢  布丽
Oh, bree.
我真为我们感到骄傲
I am so proud of us.
我是说  一开始  我们无中生有
I mean, first, we create butter out of nothing
就制成了奶油
But thin air.
呃  好吧  五加仑的牛奶和三小时的苦工
Okay, well, five gallons of milk and three hours of labor,
但是仍然  我们制成了奶油
But still-- we made butter.
而现在我们要把衣服弄得
And now we are getting our clothes
一尘不染
Squeaky clean...
而不花分毫
With nothing...
除了脏石头
But dirty rocks...
和把我皮肤伤得不浅的肥皂
And soap that I'm pretty sure is burning my skin off.
让我自己这么说吧
And if I do say so myself,
我弄了把有老妈架子的
I have dropped a butt bomb
原木梳子
Of pioneer mom on this here log comb.
哎呀
Ow!
我其实休息了一小会
I actually took a little break
把我的脚丫子放到溪水里
And cooled my toes off in the stream,
然后提神到让我的脚像被刺了一样
And it was so refreshing that it made my feet tingle.
真是爽啊
You go, girl!
那是蚂蟥吗
Are those leeches?
蚂蟥  活生生的蚂蟥
Leeches! real, live leeches!
快把那些吸血鬼弄走啊
Get these bloodsucking slugs off of me!
布丽  别愣着不动
Bree, do something!
快放开她  蚂蟥们
Get off her, leeches!
快走  快走
Shoo! shoo!
得了吧  布丽
Come on, bree.
这就是你该搭个老妈架子的地方
This is where you drop a butt bomb of mom on it.
哦  宝贝  我又不是你亲妈
Oh, honey, I'm not your mom.
别做傻事哦
Don't take this the wrong way.
我先走一步了
But I'm out of here.
难道还有不傻的事可做吗
Is there a right way to take that?